Hi I'm Joe Cuenco with Family Resources.
Today we're going to be talking about not to live the rest of our life alone.
Specifically how to choose a partner for life.
Well just how do we choose a partner or life?
Well I wish I could say that it's just as ease as going behind isle 12 in a grocery store but it's, it's not that, that, that easy.
The first thing we really need to do is take a look in the mirror.
We really need to do an introspective look and say who are we from an inventory perspective.
What do we want short term, long term and then approach it from there.
You really need to think about who we'd like to be matched up with long term that's very similar to our short term goals and our long term goals, and who we really are.
Are you looking to be with a professional?
Do you want to be with somebody's who a University Professor.
Do you want to work with somebody or be with somebody who's maybe in the architectural trades?
Or somebody's who involved in sports.
Perhaps you need to find somebody's who's, who's a marathoner because those things are important to you.
But you really need to, really need to take a look at what your, your life styles are and try and match those up with your potential partner.
The first part is really doing an introspective look in improving your own self confidence.
That comes from educating yourself; being the best person that you can be and making sure that you radiate that self confidence.
You need to find somebody that has the relationship fundamentals down.
Somebody who's going to love you, you can trust, communicate with you, respect you and be your friend for life.
And if these things are not there then you're really going to have a difficulty or difficult time moving the relationship, relationship to the next level.
The other thing is find somebody who's going to treat you special.
Do the little things for you.
Brig you a cup of coffee in the morning.
A martini at night.
Or a beer while you're watching a football game.
Or rub her shoulder or rub her feet.
Put gas in her car.
Make her eel very special.
The other thing you need to take a look at is is what level of interaction takes place with the family.
Can you get along with the family? That's an important, important thing. What are your short term goals, your long term goals?
What does your retirement look like?
Do you want children?
So you have to be aligned from that view point because if you're not then you're going to, this discongruity is going to create problems for you later on down the road.
So share the same goals.
Share the same goals in terms of your life, life style but also you need to take a look at, at cultural aspect.
Relationship work shops are very helpful here.
Family Resources puts those on.
And so this is how we learn how to choose a partner for life.
I'm Joe Cuenco with Family Resources, relationships for life.